

# **BANGOY, RICHARD JOSHUA** Undergraduate | Web Developer

General Santos City, Philippines

**&** +63 991 930 3309

### SOCIAL

in linkedin.com/in/rjshbangoy

github.com/rjshbangoy

facebook.com/r.joshua.bangoy

#### PROFILE

I am currently a 4th-Year Information Technology student at Mindanao State University - General Santos. I am 21 years old, born in Davao City, Philippines. I am a fast learner and I enjoy learning something new. My goal is to become a proficient Web Developer in the future.

#### EDUCATION

## **BS Information Technology**

Mindanao State University - General Santos 2020 - 2024

#### Senior High School

Mindanao State University - General Santos 2018 - 2020

## **Junior High School**

General Santos City SPED Integrated School 2014 - 2018

# SKILLS

- HTML/CSS
- PostgreSQL
- JavaScript
- MySQL
- ReactJS
- NodeJS
- Python
- MongoDB

#### EXPERIENCE

## Capstone Project Leader

From 2022 to 2024 | Mindanao State University - General Santos

- Led and managed a team of three in the development of the capstone project, "TRAVIS"
- Designed and maintained a comprehensive project documentation to ensure efficient team collaboration
- Collaborated as a UI/UX Assistant Designer to create an intuitive and user-friendly interface for the project
- Designed UML and Entity Relationship diagrams to provide clear visual representations of system architecture and database structures
- Designed project prototype using Figma

## EVENTS, CERTIFICATES, AND AWARDS

## Mindanao State University - General Santos Dean's Lister (2020 - 2023)

A consistent dean's lister since 2020. Currently pursuing Latin honors and is expected to graduate in June 2024.

## Participant - Digital Careers Expo (November 28, 2023)

Participated in the Digital Careers Expo in Sarangani held last November 28, 2023 at the Alabel Municipal Gymnasium.

# Participant - 11th Philippine Society of Information Technology Students Regional Summit (April 28 - 29, 2023)

Participated in the 11th PSITS held last April 28-29, 2023 at KCC Convention Center, General Santos City. Also competed in the 11th PSITS MLBB Tournament representing MSU - General Santos.

## Cisco Networking Academy - Networking Essentials Badge (June 15, 2022)

Cisco verifies the earner of this badge successfully completed the Networking Essentials course and achieved this student level credential. Participated in up to 19 labs and 24 Cisco Packet Tracer activities.

#### PROJECTS

MERN Stack Project

### **Ardrich Estate**

- A project made for the subject: ITD110 - NoSQL Databases
- The project utilized:

MongoDB, ExpressJS, ReactJS, and NodeJS

- GitHub Repository:

github.com/rjshbangoy/MERN-Project/

Website Resume

## My Resume

- A project made for the subject:
- IT183 Web Systems and Technologies
- The project utilized:
- HTML/CSS and JavaScript - GitHub Pages:
- rjshbangoy.github.io/my-resume/

## LANGUAGES

- English
- Tagalog
- Cebuano

#### INTERESTS









Music Gaming Sports

Travelling